<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Anjali Khushalani</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Anjali Khushalani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Topic Modeling</title>
      <link>/post/topic-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/topic-modeling/</guid>
      <description>What is topic modeling? Topic modeling provides an algorithmic solution to managing, organizing and annotating large archival text. The annotations aid you in tasks of information retrieval, classification and corpus exploration
 Setting up the platform to perform topic modeling You may want to consider installing these libraries using the install.packages(“packagename”) function and then calling the library
library(wordcloud) library(data.table) library(tidytext) library(dplyr) library(ggplot2) library(SnowballC) library(RTextTools) library(tm) library(wordcloud) library(topicmodels) library(slam) library(reshape2) library(ldatuning)  Data The data for this blog has been collected from psychcentral.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Buisness Intelligence class taught me?</title>
      <link>/post/what-buisness-intelligence-class-taught-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/what-buisness-intelligence-class-taught-me/</guid>
      <description>Data is the new oil. Unfortunately, the technology has evolved faster than the workforce skills to make sense of it, and organizations across sectors must adapt to this new reality or perish
Andreas Weigend, Head of Stanford’s Social Data Lab and former Chief Scientist at Amazon
I Understand the trends in BI are changing. Business Intelligence has revolutionized and will continue to do so. Five BI trends which will rule BI landscape:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>